LEONARD: Nice move.
RAJESH: I've got it.
HOWARD: Take him down.
LEONARD: He's got you, Sheldon.
HOWARD: Come on.
LEONARD: He's completely schooling you.
Hey, guys, some of the other waitresses
wanted me to ask you something.
- It's Tressling.
- It combines the physical strength...
(Howard:)...of arm wrestling with the mental agility
of Tetris into the ultimate sport.
(Penny:)That's terrific, but what they wanted me
to ask you is to cut it the hell out.
All right, come on, guys. Come on.
WAIT STAFF [SINGING]:
Happy birthday to you
(Sheldon:)We might as well stop, it's a stalemate.
(Sheldon:)You're beating me in Tetris, but you've got
the upper body strength of a Keebler elf.
(Raj:)Keebler elf?
I got a Keebler elf right here.
[RAJESH GROAN ING]
(Raj:)Okay, it's a stalemate.
(Penny:)Leonard, will we be seeing you on Saturday
for your free birthday cheesecake?
(Sheldon:)He can't eat cheesecake.
He's lactose intolerant.
(Penny:)Okay, he can have carrot cake.
- What about the cream-cheese frosting?
- He can scrape it off.
(Leonard:)Forget about the cake.
How did you know my birthday's Saturday?